All right.
好了
Let's start by looking for
首先 我们来看看
the name key in the example JSON response from the Twitter API request.
Twitter API 请求的 JSON 示例响应 中的 name 键
By searching the response for the name key,
在响应中搜索 name 键
we actually see that it appears multiple times for different uses.
事实上 我们可以看到出现了 多次使用 name 的情况
Sometimes the value is Tony Fadell.
有的值为 Tony Fadell
Sometimes the value is Sebastian Thrun, and sometimes it's Udacity.
有的值为 Sebastian Thrun 还有 Udacity
In all three cases,
在三种情况下
the value appears to be a string that represents the name of a Twitter user.
name 的值都是一个字符串 代表 Twitter 用户的名字
So in the quiz, the name key maps to the string JSON primitive.
因此在测试中 name 键映射的是 一个 JSON 原始字符串类型
Next, we'll look for the user key.
接下来 查找 user 键
The user key maps to a value that is enclosed in curly braces.
user 键所映射的值 包含在大括号中
That means it maps to a JSON object with a lot more attributes about that Twitter
也就是说 它映射到一个 JSON 对象 其中包含 Twitter 用户的诸多属性
user with the name shernazdaver, screen_name, and other information.
例如 name 为 shernazdaver、 screen_name 以及其他信息
If you look at the other cases where user appears,
如果你观察 user 出现的 其他情况
you'll find other Twitter users.
则会发现其他 Twitter 用户
So that means the user key maps to a JSON object.
由此可以说明 user 键映射的是 一个 JSON 对象
Next, we'll look for the hashtags key.
接下来 查找 hashtags 键
The hashtags key maps to a JSON array
hashtags 键映射的是一个 JSON 数组
because it points to a value with square brackets.
因为其所指的值包含在 方括号中
There's one hashtag in this tweet which is I\/O 16.
这条推文中包含 话题标签 IO 16
This is the hashtag for the 2016 Google IO conference.
这一话题标签是指 2016 年 Google IO 大会
If there are more hashtags in this tweet, they would show up in this array.
推文中若存在其他话题标签 则也会显示在此数组中
So the hashtag key maps to a JSON array.
因此 hashtags 键映射的是一个 JSON 数组
Next, we'll look for the followers_count key.
接下来 查找 followers_count 键
The key followers_count maps to the number of followers this
followers_count 键映射此 Twitter 用户 所拥有的
Twitter user has, which is 460291 in this case.
关注者数量 在本例中为 460291
So the followers count key maps to a JSON Primitive.
因此 followers_count 键映射的是 一个 JSON 原始类型
Which is an integer in this case.
在本例中为整型